我们是宝石战士
We are the Crystal Gems
本作品之片源来自互联网，仅供学习、交流之用。请自觉于下载后24小时内删除。任何组织和个人不得用于任何商业用途，否则一切后果请自行承担！如果喜欢本片，请购买正版！
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
终日拯救世界
we'll always save the day
■
时间轴： 树叶
如果你感到怀疑
and if you think we can't
我们总能找到出路
we'll always find a way
■
翻译： Chim
所以全世界人们都信任
that's why the people of this world believe in...
■
校订： 树叶
石榴  紫晶
Garnet, Amethyst...
和珍珠
and Pearl...
还有史蒂文
and Steven!
宇宙小子  第二季第八集
Steven Universe  S02E08 Reformed
形态重组
■
后期： 树叶  JlilaCY
抽泣的牛角包
Sniffling croissant!
这网站很懂我嘛
You really know me, internet.
-你们快看  -怎么了史蒂文
- Hey, guys! - Yeah, Steven?
你们应该测测我刚发现的这个在线问卷
You guys should take this online quiz I found.
它能测出
It tells you what...
测出你是“哭泣的早餐伙伴”中的哪个角色
It tells you what character you are from "Crying Breakfast Friends"!
为什么啊
- Eh... why?
从卡通形象的角度看自己很有意思啊
It's just fun to see yourself as a cartoon character.
比如  哀伤的蛋杯象征焦虑紧张
Like weeping eggcup, who's neurotic and uptight,
而憔悴的柚子是一个敏感的中年人
or pining grapefruit, the sensitive older one
他很希望自己能做个好榜样
who wishes he was a better role model.
要不等我们修好车再说吧
Uh, maybe we can do that thing after we've fixed the van.
好吧  那我先去找别人玩了
Okay. I'll go find someone else!
你听明白这个动画是什么了吗
Do you understand that cartoon show?
我什么也听不明白
I don't understand anything anymore.
史蒂文  还有多的机油吗
Hey, Steven. Is there any more engine oil?
我要用来做三明治
I need it for this sandwich.
我觉得机油是给车用的
I...think that's for cars.
好吧  那还有剩的吗
Well, is there any more of it?
我爸爸那里应该还有点
Dad's probably got some outside.
对了  你一定要测测这个在线问卷
Oh! But, uh, you got to take this online quiz.
哭泣的早餐伙伴角色对对碰
Which Crying Breakfast Friend are you?
那个节目可诡异了
That show's really weird.
谁会想看一个专门讲哭泣的卡通啊
Who wants to watch a cartoon about people crying?
-我想呀  -好吧  好吧
- I do! - Okay, okay!
第一个问题是什么
what's the first question?
-你会不会做事不过脑子  -从来不会
- Do you ever act without thinking? - Nope. Never.
你害怕冒险和尝试新事物吗
Are you afraid of taking risks and trying new things?
当然怕了
Terrified.
紫晶  你真的有在认真回答吗
Amethyst, are you taking this seriously?
-当然啊  -好吧
- Of course I am. - Okay.
你会对人际关系感到不安
Are you insecure about your relationships
或者在乎别人对你的看法吗
and how you're perceived by other people?
不会吧  还是会呢
N-N-No... Yes? Eh...
-正确答案是什么  -没有正确答案啊
- What's the right answer? - There is no right answer.
你只要如实回答就行了
You're just supposed to answer honestly.
-算了  好无聊  -等等  我还有好多
- Nah, I'm bored. - Wait ... I have loads more
更深入的的问题要问呢
probing, personal questions to ask!
石榴  你在我房间里做什么
Garnet! W-What are you doing in my room?
我看到一个腐坏的的宝石
I saw a corrupted gem.
我顺着它凿的石洞跟来的
I followed it through the tunnel it dug in the rock.
-好吧  -它从哪来的
- Yeah, right. - Where did it come from?
有点像珍珠描述的
It's similar to Pearl's description
她看到的那个偷偷潜入神庙的东西
of the creature she saw slinking through the temple.
你看到了那个潜入者吗
You saw the Slinker?!
我们明明都认同了当时没有潜入者
I thought we agreed there was no Slinker
我们也不打算叫它“潜入者”
and that we weren't going to call it "the Slinker".
是这样没错
Yes, we did.
但现在不可否认它确实存在
But now it's undeniable the creature exists
-而且史蒂文起的名还不错  -好耶
- and that Steven's name stuck. - Yes!
不  听着  你怎么不让我去找找它在哪
No! Look, why don't you just let me look for it?
因为你找不到
Because you won't.
潜入者在这里有多久了
How long's this thing been in here?
快看  史蒂文  我是一头大象
Look, Steven! I'm a pachyderm!
这里边还有小赠品呢
Oh!  And there's a prize inside!
嘘  别说话
Shhh! Keep quiet.
石榴  顽固又靠谱
Oh, Garnet. Stern but practical.
和洒出的牛奶一样
Just like spilt milk.
你不会还在想着那愚蠢的卡通吧
You're not still on about that dumb cartoon, are you?
对了  测试还没做完呢
Oh, right ... the quiz!
当别人向你问你一些隐私的问题时
Do you get defensive when people ask you questions
你会有所防备吗
about the feelings you prefer to keep hidden?
史蒂文  不要跟我玩什么心理游戏
Don't get all psycho-logical on me, Steven.
不好意思
Uh... sorry?
在这
There!
我的老天啊  你抓到了吗
Whoa, mama! Did you get it?!
没有
No.
天呐
Aw, man!
我最喜欢的球体就在这里面呢
I think my favorite round thing was in there.
我再给你个新的就是了
I'll get you a new round thing.
你折腾的都是我的东西
Ugh! This is my stuff you're messing with!
就算它们要被弄坏
If it's gonna get ... Ugh! ... wrecked,
也只能我来弄坏
I'm gonna be the one to wreck it!
看到了吗  就像这样
See?! That's how it's do...
紫晶变回原形了
Amethyst got poofed!
潜入者
Slinker!
石榴
G-G-G-Garnet?
史蒂文  你要记住  我们的身体只是幻象
Steven, remember ... our bodies are only an illusion.
紫晶会没事的
Amethyst will be fine.
但是  珍珠上次花了两个星期才复原
B-B-But Pearl took two whole weeks to come back.
而且我已经开始想念紫晶了
And I already miss Amethyst so much!
别担心  她转眼间就会回来的
Don't worry. She'll be back before you know it.
确实如此
Literally.
紫晶回来  紫晶回来了
Amethyst's back! Amethyst's back!
看起来你好像
Looks like you...
比我上次见你时多了几只脚
grew a few feet since the last time I saw you!
对你而言  恢复得真快
That was fast. Even for you.
不是问题
Eh! It's no big deal.
我只是不想让我的头号粉丝等太久
I didn't want to keep my biggest fan waiting.
好了好了  我们还要追潜入者呢
Okay, okay! We got a Slinker to slink!
如果我是个怪物  我会去哪呢
Where would I go if I was a monster?
快来这边
Hey! Over here.
-你的新形态真有趣  -谢了  史蒂文
- Your new form is really interesting. - Thanks, Steven.
我都没想到你能变形成这样
I didn't even know you could come back this different.
谢谢你  史蒂文
Thanks, Steven.
所以你为什么会带着四条腿
So, why'd you come back with four legs?
因为我喜欢走路啊
'Cause I like walking!
我也好想要四条腿
Wow. I want four legs, too!
不行  紫晶这次重组很匆忙
No, you don't. Amethyst rushed her regeneration.
-她应该慢慢来  -像珍珠一样吗
- She should have taken her time. - Like Pearl?
对  不过珍珠又稍微磨蹭了点
Yes. Pearl put a bit more... thought into how she came back.
珍珠  珍珠  又是珍珠
Pearl, Pearl, Pearl!
你们知道我听得到吧
You know I can hear you!
不好意思  我没有珍珠那样酷炫的形态
I'm sorry I'm not like Pearl with her fancy form
也没有她那样干净整洁不带怪物的房间
and her clean room with no monsters in it.
紫晶
Amethyst?
是紫晶的宝石  她又变回原形了
Amethyst's gem! She got poofed again!
这对她来说是好事
This is a good opportunity for her.
她可以变个好一点的形态了
Now she can make a better form.
她要回来了
She's coming back!
你说得没错  这个形态好多了
You're right. This is much better!
她在模仿珍珠
She's doing Pearl!
石榴  你觉得我的新造型怎么样呀
Hey, Garnet. What do you think of my new look, Garnet?
我现在看起来很像珍珠了  很棒吧
I'm more like Pearl now. Isn't it wonderful? Ha!
我觉得近乎完美
I feel... practically perfect!
我们要专心寻找潜入者的声音
We need to focus on listening for the creature.
可是我无法集中注意力
Oh, but I can't focus.
这些石头大小都不一样
All these rocks are different sizes.
我们必须按照形状和颜色排列好
We'll have to organize them by shape and color.
难道大自然不懂我喜欢什么样的石头吗
Didn't anyone tell nature how I want it to look?
别给她捧场
Don't encourage her.
但是我需要有人捧场啊  石榴
But I need encouragement, Garnet.
我需要大家对我的支持和肯定
I need everyone's constant approval.
我要不停地唠叨来引起人们的注意
I need to loquaciously converse so I can show off...
我真是机智啊
how smart I am.
你可以跟我唠叨呀  我们继续做问卷吧
You can converse with me. Let's finish that quiz.
你在行动前会精心计划吗
Do you need to plan ahead before you act?
-当然会了  -你平时会注意一些小细节吗
- Oh, thoroughly. - Do you obsess over little details?
-完全如此  -你做事真的很有条理
- Completely entirely! - Wow, you're so method.
你下一次变形的时候  可以变成我吗
Next time, can you come back as me?
这个形态并不适合你
This is not a good choice for your form.
别那么严肃  石榴  这不过是个玩笑
Lighten up, Garnet. Can't you take a joke?
这并不好笑  相反  是你让自己变得很可笑
It's not funny. You've made yourself ridiculous.
-什么 可笑  -小声点  别吓跑潜入者
- Ridiculous?! - Keep your voice down! The creature.
你希望我能跟珍珠多学学  我现在不是照做了吗
Grrr! You wanted me to be more like Pearl, and now I am!
珍珠会认真对待她的形态重组
Pearl would have taken her regeneration seriously!
关你什么事  我的形态我做主
What do you care?! My form is my business!
如果这件事影响团队的强弱  那就得我做主了
It's my business when it affects the strength of the team!
那又怎样  难道我不够强大吗
So what?! I'm not strong enough?
-紫晶  -你的是在说我不中用吗
- Amethyst! - Are you saying I'm weak?!
如果说我已经习惯这样了  是不是很奇怪
Is it weird I'm getting numb to this?
好了
Okay!
要知道  我一开始没什么感觉
You know, I wasn't feeling this at first,
但是力量现在渐渐涌上来了
but I think I might be coming around! Ha!
史小子  我的肌肉线条如何
Yo, Ste-Man. My seams straight?
你这个新形态会难受吗
Does that new form... hurt you?
没有啊  石榴
No. Hey, Garnet.
你看这混搭如何
How'd you like to mix it up with this?
我只不过是随便了组织一下  你懂
Just a little somethin' I threw together. You know.
这个形态撑不了多久的  紫晶
This form isn't sustainable, Amethyst.
但是  是你说我应该要变得更强大啊
But... you're the one who said I needed to be stronger!
好了  闯进我房间的怪物由我来收拾
Okay, if it's my monster, then I'll deal with it.
紫晶
Amethyst!
待在我身后
Stay behind me!
紫晶
Amethyst!
-快放手  -不
- Let it go! - No!
是你希望我变得更强大
You wanted me to be stronger!
我正在做呢  按照你想要的
I'm doing it! I'm being what you want!
我不想要你这样
I don't want this!
那你想要我怎样  就直说吧我会照做的
Well, what do you want?! Just tell me, and I'll do that!
我不能告诉你  紫晶
I can't tell you, Amethyst!
你必须要自己领悟出来
You have to figure this out for yourself!
她不行的  她根本不想考虑自己的事情
She can't. She doesn't want to think about herself!
什么
What?
接得漂亮
Good catch.
我就知道潜入者是存在的
I knew that thing was real!
等紫晶变回来了  我们要一起去找到它
When Amethyst gets back, we have to go find it.
-已经过去多久了  -四个小时
- How long has it been? - Four hours.
四个小时了吗  她从来没用过这么久
Four hours?! She's never taken so long.
她在里边做什么呢
What is she doing in there?
我也不知道  我之前对她太严苛了
I'm not sure. I was too hard on her.
她变回来了
Oh, oh! She's coming back!
好了  大家一定要鼓励她
All right. Everyone be supportive.
-怎么  -你几乎没有变啊
- What? - Aw, you barely changed.
史蒂文
Steven!
这样很完美
It's perfect.
无所谓了  这个形态比较合适我
Ehh, whatev. It's just what feels right.
就是因为这样才完美
It is a marked improvement.
而且有了明显改善
你终于调好肩带了  我之前一直看着不舒服
You finally fixed that shoulder strap that's always bugged me!
-欢迎回来  -干得好  紫晶
- Welcome back! - Well done, Amethyst!
别闹了
Knock it off!
我们还得去找潜入者呢
We got to go find the Slinker!
不要  现在是抱抱时间
No, it's hug time!
这真是太蠢了
Ugh! This is so dumb!
如果我能办得到
If I could begin to be,
你想象中一半的好
Half of what you think of me,
我什么都愿意做
I could do about anything,
甚至学着去爱
I could even learn how to love.
用你的方式
Like you.